

SZYMON KOWALEWSKI

DATA CONSULTANT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an enthusiast of machine learning and data analysis, with a deep passion for optimizing computer devices and creating innovative solutions using Raspberry Pi. My practical knowledge and experience in hosting services have helped me acquire a solid foundation in the field of data technology.

I am also engaged in using artificial intelligence for creating graphics and automating daily tasks

SKILLS

Python

 Scikit-learn, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, Flask Seaborn

Version Control System: <u>GI</u>

Proficient in <u>SQL</u>, including query writing, data modeling in <u>DBT</u>, data integration, and database optimization (<u>PostgreSQL</u>, <u>MySQL</u>, <u>Snowflake</u>)

 GA, GTM, Google Optimize, Segment Amplitude

Experience with BI Tools

 Tableau, Alteryx, KNIME, n8n, AppSmith Retool

Familiar with Statistical Tools:

SPSS, Statistica, gretl

PROJECTS

- ML Model for Predicting FIFA World Cup Matches in Qatar with Data Analysis in Tableau
- Image Recognition for Identifying Players of Two Teams on the Field
- End-to-End ETL Pipeline Using dbt, Airflow, and Pedshift

CONTACT

- 512 912 624
- _ szymonkowal019@gmail.com
- www.skszymon.eu













EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Data Consultant Hogart (2023 - present)

Lubaszka Bakery Shops (03.2023-06.2023)

- Developed and implemented data flows aimed at optimizing and streamlining the company's analytical processes.
- Designed and implemented two database applications (data extraction and transformations) and Business Intelligence applications using Qlik.
- Collaborated with the business team to understand their needs and tailored applications to meet specific business requirements.
- Monitored and optimized the performance of databases and applications, significantly improving the efficiency of analytical processes.

Pernord Ricard (07.2023-present)

- Managed and resolved new reports concerning changes and issues in QlikView and Qlik Sense applications.
- Implemented improvements in the code and the external layer of the application.
- Designed, created, and managed ETL processes in SAP Data Services.
- Served as the system administrator for QlikView, SAP Data Services, and Qlik NPrinting, responsible for task management, access control, and general system maintenance.
- Collaborated with various company departments to identify areas for improvement and implemented solutions to increase the efficiency of working with Qlik tools.

Junior Data Engineer No Fluff Jobs (2022 - 2023)

- Web Scraping i automatyzacja codziennych zadań w Pythonie
- Budowanie przepływów danych przy pomocy dbt, Python, Hevo, Snowflake
- Opomiarowanie produktu określanie celu i zasięgu, analiza i interpretacja wyników oraz wdrożenie (GA, GTM, Google Optimize)

Junior Data Analyst No Fluff Jobs (2020 - 2022)

- Web Scraping and Automation of Daily Tasks in Python
- Building Data Flows using dbt, Python, Hevo, Snowflake
- Product Measurement Defining objectives and scope, analyzing and interpreting results, and implementation (using GA, GTM, Google Optimize)

Data Scout Statscore (2016 - 2022)

- Creating Real-Time Graphic Match Reports
- Building Statistical Databases
- Analyzing Large Data Sets on Current On-Field Situations

EDUCATION

University of Gdansk

Computer Science and Econometrics (Data Analysis Big Data) | 2021 - 2023

• Master's Thesis: ML/DL Model for Predicting Salary Ranges in Job Offers

University of GdanskComputer Science and Econometrics

(Data Analysis) | 2018 - 2021

- Uczestnictwo oraz tworzenie wydarzeń dla społeczności IT w kole naukowym "L!der"
- Tworzenie aplikacji dot. zdalnego zamawiania muzyki w restauracjach na konkurs "Imagine Cup" z wyróżnieniem w konkursie "Startuj do STARTupu"
- Zastosowanie algorytmów uczenia maszynowego na przykładzie NCAA i AZS praca licencjacka

COURSES

Practice ML/NLP - Dataworkshop
Databricks Academy - Accenture
IoT/Network Fundamentals/CCNA R&S - Cisco
ML in Python with scikit-learn - fun-mooc
EITC/IS - EITCA Academy
SAS SCYP - SAS

Consent for Personal Data Processing I hereby give my consent for the processing of my personal data for recruitment purposes in accordance with Article 6(I)(a) of the Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council (EU) 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).